<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Hi! I&#39;m Leona</title>
    <link>https://academia-hugo.netlify.com/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Hi! I&#39;m Leona</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://academia-hugo.netlify.com/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://academia-hugo.netlify.com/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://academia-hugo.netlify.com/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a data-driven professional with a passion for global development. Previously, I was at the World Bank in Washington, D.C. analyzing satellite data to understand traffic patterns in Haiti as well as working with donor partners on development finance instruments. I was also at the Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) in Paris where I applied policy analysis to provide evidence-based recommendations to governments seeking to reform their investment policies. I obtained a Master of International Affairs degree from Columbia University’s School of International and Public Affairs (SIPA) with a focus on economic development policy and I am currently completing an Advanced Certificate in Applied Data Science and Informatics at the NYU Tandon School of Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am interested in applying the following tools and techniques to help solve poverty and development challenges:
&lt;strong&gt;data science&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;data visualization&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;spatial analysis&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>https://academia-hugo.netlify.com/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://academia-hugo.netlify.com/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
